Thomas J Lazore

Software Developer

Address Savannah, GA, 31410

Phone 315-778-6632

E-mail tomlazore@gmail.com

Full stack software developer certified from Georgia Tech Coding Boot Camp. Experience working with technologies such as JavaScript, Express, and Node in the development of group and solo projects. A background as a paramedic has sharpened skills to be an effective team member as well as resourceful independent worker.

Projects

Never Alone | github.com/tlaze/NeverAlone

- **Description:** Team of 4 members developing a social media website geared towards mental health.
- Responsibilities: Creating, editing, and deleting posts | Mobile Responsiveness.
- **Technology Used:** Bootstrap|Javascript|Node|Express|Handlebars|Express-Session|MySQL2|Sequelize|bcrypt|Heroku|Nodemailer

Tech Blog | github.com/tlaze/tech-blog

- **Description:** Forum based application for creating posts, updating, and deleting posts.
- Technology Used: Bootstrap|Javascript|Node|Express|Handlebars|Express-Session|MySQL2|Sequelize|bcrypt|Heroku

Weather Dashboard | github.com/tlaze/weather-dashboard

- Description: Fetches data from a third party API to display current and future weather conditions for cities that users enter.
- **Technology Used:** HTML|CSS|Bootstrap|Javascript|JQuery|OpenWeatherOneAPI|Local Storage

Education

2021-09 - Full Stack Coding Boot Camp
2021-12 Coording Institute of Technology Atlanta

Georgia Institute of Technology - Atlanta, GA

2018-09 - Computer Science 2019-09

Monroe Community College - Rochester, NY

- Relevant Coursework Completed: Intro to Computer Science with Java & Programming with Python
- Completed a summer internship with Rochester Institute of Technology working on the front-end development of an application that recognizes handwritten mathematical formulas and converts it into searchable queries.

Work History

2020-03

2017-09 - Paramedic

Irondequoit Ambulance, Irondequoit, NY

- Triaged injuries by communicating with patients, bystanders and family members, and identified appropriate medical facility for transport.
- Used EMSCharts to accurately document services provided to reduce liability and improve patient

2019-05 - Research Assistant Intern 2019-08

Rochester Institute Of Technology, Rochester, NY

- Presented technical research results to diverse audiences through written, visual and oral media.
- https://www.cs.rit.edu/~dprl/mathseer/